Guide to the William Rufus Shafter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII - Printed Reference
  - Copies (Box 8, Folder 80)
Glenn, George E. Col. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19
Gloucester (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 25 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Goff, Charles J. Capt. Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Goldwater, Morris Roll VI Folder 53
Gomez, Maximo Maj. Gen., Cuban Forces Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 15 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Gonzales, Carlos Col., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24
Gonzales, Stephen M. Surg. Roll IV Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 52
Goodfellow, Dr. George Roll III Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31
Goodrich, Casper F. Capt., U. S. N. Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Goodridge, Lauretta Ransome Roll VI Folder 53
Gordon, James Col., Confederate Army Roll IV Folder 30
Governor's Island, New York Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
Grand Army of the Republic Roll III Folder 26 Roll V Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 56, Folder 57
Grand Duchess (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 39
Grandprey, Clement de Military Attache, France Roll VI Folder 52
Grant (U. S. Transport) Roll VI Folder 53
Grape Vine Bridge, Virginia Roll I Folder 8
Greeley, Adolphus W. Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 43
Greene, Francis V. Col. Roll II Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 50
Greene, Frank Maj. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 48
Greene, Henry A. Maj., A. A. G. Roll VI Folder 54
Greenleaf, Charles R. Col. Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31 Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 51
Greenwood, [?] Roll I Folder 2, Folder 7
Grimes, George S. Capt. Roll I Folder 2 Roll III Folder 23, Folder 24 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll VI Folder 57
Groesbeck, Stephan W. Maj., Judge Advocate Roll II Folder 13 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 52
Groves, J. F. Roll II Folder 14, Folder 18
Guantánamo, Cuba Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44
Guasimas, Battle of Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Guasimas, Cuba Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 22
Guerillas (Spanish) Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44
Guiteras, John Maj., Surg. Roll I Folder 10 Roll III Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 39 Roll VI Folder 51
Gulf, Department of the Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15 Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48
Gussie (U. S. Steamer) Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 20 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll VI Folder 52
Haines, George Roll II Folder 14
Hale, Edward Everett Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 65
Hall, Robert H. Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 19
Hall, William P. Col. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13
Hamilton, John M. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19
Hammer, William H. Maj. Roll I Folder 10
Hancock (U. S. Transport) Roll VI Folder 53
Harbach, Abram A. Lt. Col. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37, Folder 38
Harper, J. Henry Roll VI Folder 52
Harper's New Monthly Magazine Roll VI Folder 53
Harper's Weekly Roll I Folder 10 Roll VI Folder 52
Harper, William R. Roll V Folder 48
Harries, George H. Col. Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 45
Harris, Henry S. Maj., Surg. Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 39
Harrison, Harry Roll I Folder 8
Harvard (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Hartwick, Edward E. Lt. Roll II Folder 14
Haskell, Joseph F. Lt. Col. Roll V Folder 45
Haskell, Charles C. Roll V Folder 45
Havana, Cuba Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 35, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 53
Havard, Valery Lt. Col., Surg. Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 51
Hawkins, G. T. Roll IV Folder 31
Hawkins, Hamilton S. Brig. Gen., U. S. V. Roll II Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35
Hayes, Rutherford B. President, U. S. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4
Hayes, Webb C. Maj. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13 Roll III Folder 28 Roll VI Folder 54
Hayme, Louis R. U. S. Consul, Guadalupe Roll IV Folder 36
Hayward, George A. A. D. C. Roll I Folder 1
Hazen, William B. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50
Hearst, William R. Roll VI Folder 55
Heistand, Henry O. S. Roll V Folder 41
Helena (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Helmick, C. A. Lt. Roll VI Folder 49
Henry, Guy V. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
Hernandez, Carlos Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 17
Hibben, John G. President of Princeton Roll VI Folder 54
Hill, [?] Roll VI Folder 50
Hoar, George P. Roll V Folder 45, Folder 47
Hobson, Richmond P. Lt., U. S. N. Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Holley, Dwight E. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Holmes, Grandma Roll I Folder 8
Holquin, Cuba Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Holt, Asa Lt. Col., Paymaster Roll I Folder 1
Hood's Regiment (Col. D. B. Hood) Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 40
Hooker, Mr. and Mrs. Roll I Folder 8
Hoover, Charles S. Lt. Roll V Folder 40
Hopkins, George A. Roll VI Folder 53
Hoppin, Curtis B. Capt. Roll III Folder 19
Hornet (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Horton, William E. Capt. Roll IV Folder 37
House of Representatives, Havana, Cuba Roll VI Folder 57
House Resolution 302 Roll VI Folder 52
Howard, George W. Bvt. Maj., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Howze, Robert L. Lt. Roll II Folder 13
Hubert, Edgar Capt. Roll II Folder 16
Hudson, Marion Roll I Folder 7
Hudson (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 26, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 32 Roll V Folder 44
Humphrey, Charles F. Lt. Col., Quartermaster Roll I Folder 2, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Hunker, J. J. Commander, U. S. N. Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 20
Hunt, Clyd D. Y. Roll I Folder 10
Hunt, Levi P. Capt. Roll I Folder 7
Huntsville, Alabama Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Hutchins, Morris C. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31
Hutson, Thomas Roll VI Folder 50
Iglesias-Valdez, [?] Roll I Folder 4
Immen, George L. Roll V Folder 42
Immunes Roll II Folder 14 Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 45
Indiana (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Indians Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 7
Insurgents, Cuban Roll I Folder 10, Folder 11 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 53, Folder 54
Iowa (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Irish, E. M. A. G. of Michigan Roll II Folder 14
Irons, James A. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Iroquois (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36 Roll VI Folder 52
Isabel la Católica Batallónde Roll III Folder 27
Isla de Luzón (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44
Isla de Panay (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 39 Roll V Folder 44
Island of Pines Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32
Ives, Frank J. Maj., Surg. Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Jacobs, Joshua W. Maj. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 51, Folder 53
Jackson, William P. Lt. Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37
Jacksonville, Florida Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17
Jacksonville Times Union (Newspaper) Roll II Folder 16
Japanese Army Roll III Folder 20
Japanese Navy Roll III Folder 20
Jarvis, Samuel M. Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43
Jefferson, Fort (Dry Tortugas) Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13
Jewell, Fort Roll I Folder 4
Johnson, Arthur Lt. Roll III Folder 19, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 44
Johnson, R. U. Roll V Folder 45
Johnson, Richard W. Bvt. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1
Jones, Hamilton Act. Asst. Surg. Roll V Folder 47
Jones, Thaddeus W. Lt. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 7 Roll III Folder 27, Folder 28
Journal of the American Medical Association Roll V Folder 45
Juragua Iron Company Roll I Folder 9 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 44
Juraguacito, Cuba Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22
Juraguo Railroad Roll II Folder 18
Kalamazoo, Michigan Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Kanawha (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 38, Folder 39
Kane, Thomas L. Bvt. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 3
Kane, Woodbury Lt. Roll V Folder 45
Kautz, August V. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 8
Kellogg, Edgar R. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 12 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Kelly, J. M. Capt. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 7
Kelton, John C. A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
Kemper, Louis Roll V Folder 42
Kennan, George Roll III Folder 28
Kennedy, John Sgt. Roll III Folder 28
Kennedy, Dr. J. T. Roll V Folder 42
Kennedy, William B. Capt. Roll I Folder 6, Folder 7
Kent, Jacob F. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 15, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Kentucky, Army of Roll I Folder 1
Ketlin, Issac C. Roll IV Folder 35
Kettle, F. W. Newsman Roll II Folder 16
Kettle Hill Roll VI Folder 54
Keyes, Alex T. B. Capt. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6
Key West, Florida Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27 Roll VI Folder 57
Kickapoo (Indians) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 5, Folder 6
Kilbourne, Henry S. Maj., Surg. Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 45
Kimball, Amos S. Col. Roll IV Folder 39 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
King, Dr. [Henry C.?] Roll I Folder 4
Kingston Cable Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 34
Kirkman, George W. Lt. Roll IV Folder 35
Knickerbocker, Mrs. E. E. (Elvira Holcombe) Roll IV Folder 30
Knickerbocker (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20 Roll IV Folder 36 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45
Knight, John T. Capt. Roll V Folder 45
Lacret, [?] Gen. Roll II Folder 12
Lafayette, Marquis de Roll II Folder 14
La Garde, Louis A. Maj., Surg. Roll I Folder 10 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 51
Lakes, Department of the Roll V Folder 45
Lamadriel, [?] Maj., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 23
Lamb, Thomas Roll I Folder 4, Folder 7
Langdon, Russell C. Lt. Roll IV Folder 35 Roll VI Folder 51
Langdon, Loomis L. Col. Roll IV Folder 35 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51
Las Guasimas, Cuba Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23 Roll VI Folder 57
Lassiter, William Capt. Roll V Folder 46
Latimer, William G. Maj. Roll III Folder 27
Lauman, George V. Lt. Col. Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 41
Laura (U. S. Lighter) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 38 Roll VI Folder 57
Laurienne, [?] Roll IV Folder 35
Lawn, Charles H. Roll VI Folder 50
Lawrence, W. I. Act. Asst. Surg. Roll III Folder 19
Lawson, Cloudy Roll VI Folder 50
Lawton, Henry W. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Lawton, Louis B. Lt. Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 37
Leach Lake Indians Roll VI Folder 54
Lebo, Thomas C. Capt., Maj. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7, Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Lee, Andrew Governor of South Dakota Roll VI Folder 53
Lee, A. H. Capt., English Army Roll II Folder 16 Roll VI Folder 50
Lee, Arthur H. Capt., Military Attache, England Roll VI Folder 52
Legget, Henry F. Lt. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 7
Lehigh Valley Railroad Roll V Folder 45
Leitch, Joseph D. Capt. Roll VI Folder 53
Leon XIII (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 39
Leona (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 52
Lerdo de Tejada, Miguel M. President of Mexico Roll I Folder 4
Lewis, Edward M. Lt. Roll III Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 38
Lewis, Walter D. Roll III Folder 28
Leyden (U. S. Tug) Roll I Folder 10 Roll III Folder 28
Libby Prison, Richmond, Virginia Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 57
Liebven, Poince Capt., Naval Attache, Russia Roll VI Folder 52
Linares, Arsenio Gen., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 41 Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 56
Lincoln, Abraham President of U. S. Roll VI Folder 53
Lindsay, James R. Lt. Roll IV Folder 36
Lipan (Apache Indians) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7 Roll IV Folder 37
Liscum, Emmerson H. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 12
Logan, John A., Sr. Maj. Roll I Folder 10
Logan, John A. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 37, Folder 40
Long, John D. Sect. of the Navy Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 40, Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Long Island Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48
Longora, Julian Roll I Folder 4
Lópes, Narciso Roll IV Folder 36
Lopez de Castillo, Pedro Infantaria Espanol Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44
Lora, [?] Gen., [? Forces] Roll III Folder 28
Lord, F. G. Capt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41
Los Angeles Times (Newspaper) Roll I Folder 8
Louisiana (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 36, Folder 38
Louisville Commercial (Newspaper) Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53
Loyal Legion of the United States Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 55, Folder 57
Ludington, Marshall I. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 53
Ludlow, William Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 25, Folder 27, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 53, Folder 54
Luque, [?] Gen., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 24
Lusk, James L. Capt. Roll II Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 15
Lyman, Robert Roll I Folder 9
Lyons, John Roll V Folder 42
McAlexander, Ulysses G. Capt. Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41
McArthur, Arthur Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13
McCabe, [?] Spy Roll I Folder 4
McCaleb, Thomas S. Capt. Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36
McCalla, [?] Commodore, U. S. N. Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 44
McCaskey, William S. Maj. Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37, Folder 38
McClernand, Edward J. Lt. Col., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 19, Folder 20 Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38 Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 55
McClure, [?] Maj., Paymaster Roll I Folder 10
McCook, Reverend Henry C. Roll V Folder 43
McCormic, Lloyd S. Capt. Roll V Folder 46
McCrary, William Sect. of War Roll I Folder 4 Roll VI Folder 1
McCreery, George Maj. Roll II Folder 13
McDermott, J. E. P. Roll III Folder 28 Roll VI Folder 54
McGurrin, William T. Col. Roll II Folder 17
McKavett, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 1
McKay, James O. Capt. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 26 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 57
McKeever, Chauncy A. A. G. Roll I Folder 1
McKibbin, Chambers Lt. Col., Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 39
McKinley, William President of U. S., 1897 - 1901 Roll I Folder 8, Folder 9 Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18, Folder 19, Folder 22, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
McKittrick, Mary Shafter Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8, Folder 9 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 55, Folder 57
McKittrick, William A., Sr. Roll I Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 55
McKittrick, William H., Jr. Capt., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 8, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55, Folder 56
McLaughlin, John H. Roll I Folder 8
McLaughlin, William B. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
McLeary, James Maj., I. G. Vols. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
McMillan, James H. Capt. Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 47
McNair, [?] Rear Admiral Roll VI Folder 57
McPherson, Fort (Georgia) Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19
McQuiston, Charles Lt. Roll II Folder 49
McRae, James H. Lt. Roll IV Folder 38
Mackenzie, Ranald S. Col. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 8
Mackey, John T. Roll IV Folder 37
Mackey, I. W. Roll VI Folder 53
Maco, Antonio Gen. Roll IV Folder 36
Magoon, Charles E. Provisional Governor of Cuba Roll VI Folder 55
The Maine (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16
Malarial Fever Roll III Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 51, Folder 53, Folder 57
Mallory Steamship Line Roll II Folder 11
Malvern Hill, Battle of Virginia Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Manilla, Philippine Islands Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Manitoba (U. S. Ship) Roll V Folder 48
Mann, M. W. Roll III Folder 26
Manning (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 25
Mansas, Antonio Post Commander, Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 25
Mansaz, Antonio Lt. Roll III Folder 25
Manteo (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 38, Folder 39
Manzanillo, Cuba Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 27, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 57
Marblehead (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 33
Marcus (Mallory Line Steamer) Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12
Margaret (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 19
Maria Teresa (Spanish Ship) Roll III Folder 22, Folder 25
Marie (Neutral Steamer) Roll IV Folder 36
Marine Hospital Service of U. S. Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 48
Markley, Alfred C. Maj. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45
Marsh, C. M., Esquire President of Polk County Fair Association Roll V Folder 48
Marsh, L. A. President of Polk County Fair Association Roll I Folder 18
Marshall, Edward Roll III Folder 23
Marshall, James M. Lt. Col. Roll VI Folder 54
Martin, J. L. Roll I Folder 7
Martin, J. P. Gen. Roll I Folder 2
Martinez, [?] Lt., Mex. Forces Roll I Folder 7
Maso, Bartolome President, Republic of Cuba Roll V Folder 42
Mason, Fort (California) Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 53, Folder 54
Mason, Ino Lt. I. G. Roll I Folder 5
Mason, Victor Louis Roll VI Folder 50
Mason, William E. Senator Roll I Folder 8
Massachusetts (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Massachusetts Voluntary Aid Association Roll IV Folder 36
Massey, Solon F. Roll V Folder 44
Master of Maria (Spanish Ship) Roll IV Folder 40
Mata, Jose Maria Roll I Folder 5
Mateawan (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52
Matt, Virginia B. Roll IV Folder 37
Mauermann, B. J. Roll I Folder 8
Mavernick, George Roll I Folder 8
Maverick (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 12 Roll IV Folder 38
Maxfield, Joseph E. Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18
Maxwell, J. M. Reporter Roll II Folder 16
Medal of Honor Roll VI Folder 54
Meikeljohn, George De Rue Asst. Sect. of War Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 36 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Mendoza, Ramon G. Capt., Interpreter, A. D. C. to Lawton Roll III Folder 22, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 57
Menocal, Frank E. Act. Asst. Surg. Roll III Folder 27 Roll V Folder 47
Mercedes Hospital Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23
The Merchants Association of New York Roll V Folder 46
Merriam, Henry C. Gen. Roll VI Folder 52
Merrimac (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32 Roll VI Folder 54
Merritt, Wesley Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 13 Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 51
Mescalero (Apache) Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6
Mestre, [?] Interpreter Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23